

# **GEORGE BANLAKI**

# **INFO**



### **Address**

26 Thorn Apartments, 5 Geoff Cade Way, E34GJ



#### Phone

+44 7469 201579



#### Email

george.banlaki@gmail.com

# **SKILLS**

IT skills (Word, Excel, Outlook, Opera)

HTML / CSS

Javascript

Python

Communication skills

**Service Orientation** 

**Time Management** 

**Adobe Photoshop** 

# **OBJECTIVE**

A hardworking, reliable and conscientious person with a diverse range of customer service experience. Good team player and able to use own initiative to achieve company objectives. Versatile and learns new tasks/skills quickly and able to work well under pressure.

# **EXPERIENCE**

# LUGGAGE PORTER/CONCIERGE ASSISTANT • LONDON MARRIOTT HOTEL PARK LANE • APRIL 2017 - SEPTEMBER 2020

Provide knowledge of the local area and hotel, positively engage
with guests, colleagues and our service providers, assist guests with
their luggage, assist with rooming and offer further assistance, book
tickets, tours, car service, assist with restaurant recommendations
and bookings.

# NIGHT PORTER • LONDON MARRIOTT HOTEL PARK LANE • APRIL 2016 - APRIL 2017

• Answered Concierge relating emails, in charge of In Room Dining and Housekeeping at night, Delivered food and beverages, amenities.

# LAUNDRY PORTER • LONDON MARRIOTT HOTEL PARK LANE • FEBRUARY 2016 - APRIL 2016

• Guest and staff laundry management, received and stored deliveries, assisted with any housekeeping request.

# KITCHEN PORTER • LONDON MARRIOTT HOTEL PARK LANE • JUNE 2014 - APRIL 2015

• Kept kitchen clean and sanitized, Assisted with food preparation, washing all cooking tools.

# **OPEN WATER LIFEGUARD • LAKE BALATON • MAY 2013 - SEPTEMBER 2013**

• Keeping the beach area clean, supervising swimmers at all times.

# **EDUCATION**

### 2021

NPLQ (National Pool Lifeguard Qualification)

## 2021

**CODING COURSE - Career Switch** 

#### 2020

**HEALTH AND SAFETY AWARENESS** 

#### 2019

**EMERGENCY FIRST AID AT WORK** 

### 2019

MANUAL HANDLING

## 2019

**GLOBAL SECURITY TIER 1-2-3** 

### 2017

FOOD HANDLING TRAINING

### 2011

CSIK FERENC HIGH SCHOOL BUDAPEST